timed the time loan time uh How long does it take for
засека время заем вре ээ За сколько тает
snow to melt Come on snow
снег Давай снег
Come on don't pull it tight I really
Давай ты его не обтягивать я реально
want to see How long does it take for it
хочу посмотреть За сколько времени он
to melt will it melt for you at all Is there
растает он растает у вас вообще Снег
snow no we've never had snow us
есть нет у нас никогда не было снега нас
Niko There was no
Нико Не было
snow And we have snow you  don't throw off
снега А у нас есть снег ты не скидывай
the snow I set the stopwatch I'm
снег я секундомер поставил мне
interested interesting
интересном
Hello Hello Great And what is this
Здравствуйте Здорово А что за след от
footprint imprint
ноги отпечаток
Here where And all this hair there I think it's a
Тут где А всё это волосы ту я думаю это
trace like a kick with a sole
След типа как пнули подошвой
this Barskoe pole I got it And you have strong
это Барское поле понял А у тебя силь
hairiness I have it normal too but I
волосатость у меня вот норм тоже но я
cooler I have more testosterone
круче У меня тестостерона больше
more testosterone well well it's clear that
тестерона больше ну ну понятно что
you yourself are like Well
ты сам как А ну покажи
show me there is
же есть по груди покажи
hair on your chest show me I'm cooler And do you have hair on your back do
волос у меня круче А на спине есть у
you have hair
тебя воло у тебя волос
pain Yes I have more hair I'm cooler
боль Да у меня волос больше я круче
man
мужик
look me Wait And you  You
смотри ме Подожди А ты в подъезде
're sitting in the entryway, but it's
сидишь да
not me I won't lie
не я тея Врать не буду
Here you are, naked, sitting in the
Вот ты голый сидишь в
entryway Show me what's in your
подъезде Покажи что в труха
pants
нах в штанах
Yash pants And everything in pants everything I got scared
Яш штаны А всё в штанах всё Я испугался
everything
всё
Yes, you're not a normal
Да не ты нормальный
person I'm just looking at a naked man in the
человек я просто смотрю голый мужик в
entryway I thought you were completely naked I think you
подъезде думал ты вообще голый думаю
got scared
испугался
[music]
[музыка]
koto yahva Noah man a Listen,
кото яхва Ной человек а Слушай а
what city are you in, it's not cold in the
ты в каком городе у вас не холодно в
entryway we're not there
подъезде нас нет
and where are you from
а ты сам откуда
Kazakhstan
будешь Казахстан
Almaty normal r beautiful Listen but
Алмааты нормальный р красивый Слушай а
really Show me how it is outside the window or is there Do
реально Покажи как за окном или есть У
you have snow show me through the window or is there Do
вас снег покажи через окошко или есть У
you have snow snow snow yes Now I'll show
вас снег сне снег да Сейчас я покажу
you now And now I'll show you
сечас А сейчас я тебе покажу снег
there is snow snow no here in Almaty  there is no
есть снег нет у нас в Алматы нету снега
snow snow What are you talking about there is no snow there is no snow
снега Да ты что у вас там не снега нет у
here it is warm hot plus 20 P 20 And here it is
нас тепло жара плю 20 П 20 А у нас
the opposite minus Minus
наоборот минус Минус
10 snow is lying yes Well I haven't
10 снег лежит да Ну я снега не
seen any snow Wait now I'll go down I'm already opening the door
видел Подожди сейчас я спущусь уже дверь
Look come on come to which one is this
Вот смотри а ну подойди к какому это
really
реально
snow yes it is snow take it in your
снег да это снег возьми его в
hand here I am standing here
руку вот я стою вот вот
snow is not closer well come to the snowdrift
снег не ближе ну к сугробу снега подойди
so that I can get close to it  looked Now
чтобы я с близка его посмотрел Сейчас
wait I'll look I have a key from under
подожди я клю посмотрю у меня от под
and VS there is there is
есть а ВС есть есть
ri Here
ри Вот
look tanu he te atri if it's snow
смотри тану он те атри если это снег
try atri He will tanut melt on
попробуй атри Он будет тануть таять об
you atri itself
тебя атри себя
look Yes it won't melt it's not snow snow
смотри Да он не танет это не снег сне
It's
Это
snow it's snow it's u  you just
снег это снег это у вас просто снега
don't have snow I've never seen snow I've seen it
нет я никогда снега не видел видел
look
смотри
how
ка
cold it is Can you wipe yourself with
холодный А ты можешь обтереть весь
snow I can't because I have a
снегом я не могу потому что у меня в
phone in one hand Well okay
одной руке телефон Ну хорошо вот этой
wipe yourself with this hand and rub yourself really hard I
рукой обори ещё сильно себя обори Мне
wonder how it will melt really
интересно как оно растает реально
cold
холодный
snow of course is cold
снег конечно холодный
And how
А как
good Oh you
хорошо-то Ах ты
Oh well it can't be cold snow I
Да ну это не может быть холодный снег Я
don't believe that you just
не верю что ты так просто холодным
wipe yourself with cold snow I'm telling you I have
снегом обтирается обра Я тебе говорю у
snow right next to me I
меня вот рядом вот снег вот я снегом
wipe myself with snow how cold And can you eat
обтирать как холодно А ты можешь есть
something if it is  snow can you show
какой-то если это снег можешь показать
that you will lie down in a snowdrift that there really is a
что ты ляжешь в сугроб что действительно
snowdrift there is snow there is not a snowdrift with us
сугроб снега есть снега есть не у нас
now there is not a snowdrift yet we still
сейчас сугроб Пока ещё нет у нас ещ мало
have little snow somewhere where here  smooth snow
выпало снега где-то где вот ровный снег
can you show what depth
ты можешь вот что показать какая глубина
here lie on
вот лечь на
it depth we don't even have depth now
него глубина у нас даже глубины нет
snow please There's
сечас снега пожалуйста Вон на детской
snow on the playground anyway Let's go let's
площадке по-любому есть снег Давай идм
go to the playground Come on let's
идём на детскую площадку Давай давай я
tell you again We don't have any snow
те ещё раз говорю У нас сейчас снега нет
yet  Well, let's go, let's go to the
пока Ну пошли пошли подойдём на детскую
playground, we have a little bit of snow,
площадку чуть-чуть у нас чуть-чуть снег
show us on the deck, on the children's
выпал покажи на декой жи на детй
playground, there's a little bit of snow there, near the bench,
пло Во вот там возле скамейки немножко
try to lie down on the snow, snow No, I
Попробуй лечь на снег сне Нет я этого
won't do that because I'm not in the
делать не буду потому что это я не в
bathhouse, bub, I  in the bathhouse I'm now good obori
бане буб я в бане я сейчас хорошо обори
more obori because it really
ещё обори потому что он действительно
melts so what are you Oh
тает так да ты что О
look you can easily smear your head completely
смотри голову полностью можешь
I'll even go into the entrance it will melt no no
Я в подъезд даже зайду будет таять не не
I'm interested if it melts on the
Мне интересно ли он таят на
street And it won't melt on the street
улице А на улице таять не буде Потому
Because now at  us minus p and what city is this
что сейчас у нас минус п а это какой
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
Samara, I'm telling you Look, I'll
Самара вот я тебе говорю Смотри сейчас я
come in now and there will be snow  fall thief
зайду и сейчас снег будет падать тать А
Come on let's
ну давай
wait
ждём засека
time How long does it take for snow to melt Come on
время За сколько тает снег Давай
don't you tighten it I really
давай ты его не обтягивать я реально
want to see How long does it take for it
хочу посмотреть За сколько времени он
to melt will it
растает он
melt for you at all Is there snow no we've
растает у вас вообще Снег есть нет у нас
never had snow there was no
никогда не было снега не было
snow we have snow you don't  snow I
снега у нас есть сне ты не ский снег я
set a stopwatch I'm interested
секундомер поставил мне интересно
interesting here look I Time
интересно вот смотри я Засекай за
how long it will take it to melt melt oh maybe
сколько он это растает растает о может
it will Melt fast Yes yes I see it's already
он Растай быстрый Да да я смотрю уже он
starting to drip a little Yes
начинает капать немножко Да
yes we just have such a heat we have
да у нас просто у нас жара такая у нас
p20 all winter we never have snow  it doesn't
п20 всю зиму у нас снега никогда не
happen I just envy the Russians that
бывает Я просто Аж завидую русским что у
you have snow and snow and you came and
вас есть снег и снег а ты приезжал
saw snow Damn, I would have come This is in
видишь снег Блин я бы приехал Это в сама
Samara itself yes yes
в Самару да да
you can not that you can come to
ты можешь не то ты можешь приехать в
any city and go down a hill in the
любой город и с горки покататься на
snow It seems to me
снегу Мне кажется мне
it seems to me  I really don't believe that you
кажется реально я не верю что у вас
always have snow like this,
всегда такой
we don't have snow once a year. Listen, maybe.
снег нет у нас раз год снег Слушай може
I think you'll come up with it. You can
Мне кажется ты это придумаешь можешь
call one of your neighbors so that they can
кого-то из соседей позвонить чтобы они
confirm that it's like that too.  do you
подтвердили тоже что это у вас
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
really call your neighbor so that they
действительно соседе позвонить чтобы они
confirm I really am interested in a person
подтвердили мне действительно человеку
from Kazakhstan or is it
из Казахстана интересно или
really always like this snow or did
действительно всегда такой снег или это
you come up with it I didn't come up with it now to be
ты придумал придумал не я те сейчас
honest I can't
честно сказать я те не могу никому
call anyone because I don't talk to them
позвонить потому что я с теми не
I fell on my slippers A  that you
разговариваю упал на тапочки А что ты с
don't talk to them
ними не разговариваешь
I'm just not the kind of person who talks
Просто я не тот человек который общается
about all sorts of topics
на всякие темы
That is, you're an intellectual you're not interested in talking to this
То есть вы интеллектуал вам с этим не
yes yes you said everything right well I
да да ты правильно всё сказал ну я
see how intelligent an intelligent
видите как интеллигентно интеллигентного
person is I immediately see so a
человека сразу вижу так уже прошло
minute and a half has already passed but the snow is still holding on
полторы минуты но снег ещё держится
interesting look At me there it detects yes
интересно смотри Во меня вон засекает да
yes well not a mug we will completely watch it
да ну не ряха мы полностью посмотрим
detects a scientific experiment I'm just a
засекает научный эксперимент Я просто я
climatologist yes I study climate
климатолог да я изучаю климатические
Global warming and I'm interested in
Глобальное потепление и мне интересно
how much
насколько
the snow melts By the way I have 18 years of practice And
снег тает У меня кстати 18 лет прак И
in a year there will be a
через года будет
chka 2 minutes 2 minutes tat this is  like the
чка 2 минуты 2 минуты тат это как
glaciers of Antarctica are melting too Now
ледники Антарктиды тают также Вот сейчас
you see Global warming they are
видите Глобальное потепление они очень
starting to
быстро начинают
melt very quickly not me my body is burning and it is
таять не у меня ня тело горящее и оно
faster Well now let's see this ABE
быстрее Ну сейчас посмотрим вот этот АБЕ
when from where
когда отколе нетель
I see Yes I see
я вижу Да я вижу
Yes you don't understand too normal such a
Да не понимаешь тоже нормальный такой
person failure it's interesting to talk about that
человек сбой интересно поговорить о том
about
о
everything not I'm also glad that I met you
всём не Я тоже рад что тебя встретил
Because here there are some
Потому что тут встречаются какие-то
Just you are quite an interesting person I
Просто ты довольно Интересный человек я
you showed me snow I really I  I've
вот ты мне снег показал я реально я
only seen this snow in fairy tales in films about
только в сказках видел эти в фильмах про
Santa Claus and here there's real snow it's
Деда Мороза снег а тут реальный снег это
just cool it's unbelievable
просто круто это Невероятно
that we go to the bathhouse and dive into the snow and then pour cold water over ourselves and climb in the snow and
что мы мы в баню ходим и ныряем в снег
roll around in the snow and then pour
лазим снегу повалялся потом ещё с
cold water over ourselves and go into the bathhouse
холодной водой облился заходишь в баню
a mug of cold beer cold beer on the
кружку пива холодного холодного пивка на
chest slammed and went to the bathhouse
грудь хлопнул и в баню
nose no go
пошёл нос нет схо
yes I hear I I don't believe Yes everything everything I
да слышу я я не верю Да всё всё у меня
had a sound I say I don't believe that a person
звук был я говорю я не верю что человек
can pour cold water
может облиться холодной водой
there here I have right now here let's say
там вот у меня вот сейчас здесь допустим
a minute
мину
1520 we  we arrive at another place And there A
1520 мы приезжаем в другое место А там А
lie there already mi
врак там уже ми
32 We'll roll around in the snow from the bathhouse we'll come out with
32 Мы в снегу поваляемся с баньки выйдем
cold
холодной
water and cold beer
водойм холодного Пива
let's have a drink it's a
попьём это
tradition when you come to Russia I'll teach you
традиция приедешь в Россию я те научу
how to be
как быть
Russian roll around in the snow pour
русским поваляться в снегу облиться
cold water over yourself and have a
холодной водой и холодного пивка
mug of cold beer and then
кружечку и ещё
have a bite of fish after you've
рыбку рыбкой закусил после того как
slammed the mug down with fish XXX
хлопнул рыбкой ХХХ
and you're a nice
а ты приятный ты
person listen come on go to
человек слуша Давай выезжай в
Russia listen I'll come too  5 minutes
Россию Слушай я приеду тоже уже 5 минут
have passed and the snow is still there This is your
прошло а снег ещё держится Вот это у вас
snow, it's just awful Well there is snow here
снег прям капец а Ну тут есть снег
Show us have you seen snow
Покажи вот у нас снег ты видел
yes And you
да А у вас на снега
don't have snow How can I say there is no snow
нет как жа снега нет сне
Snow is nice On the other hand snow is
снег это приятно с другой стороны снег -
unpleasant to clean
неприятно убирать
clean near the house clean take a
чистить возле дома убирать берёшь лопату
wide shovel and go go
широкую и пошёл пошёл Снег
Clean the snow good man and you are also
чистить хороши человек да и ты тоже
cool just we found each other soul to soul
классный просто мы Как душа в душу нашли
I will definitely come to Samara this is
Я обязательно приеду в Самару это блин
just damn now my dream I want to
просто сама теперь моя мечта Я хочу
see the snow roll around Here is this in the snow
увидеть снег поваляться Вот это в снегу
to pour on myself  but really you
вылить на себя вот а реально вы воду
can You can pour cold water on yourself
можете Ты можешь на себя воду холодную
not Well if you want come to the
вылить не Ну если хочешь приезжай в сам
people themselves you  you will see not only snow You
народ ты увидишь не только снег Ты
can show up on a
можешь показаться на
snowboard then it's like a
сноуборде потом это как
snowboard and a
о сноуборд и
parachute you take a couple you take a snowboard
парашют берёшь пара берёшь сноуборд
you take a parachute and across the field Phew and off we go Well,
берёшь парашют и по полю Фух и погнал Ну
this is also a winter snowboard Tosh it's you with a
также это зимний сноуборд Тош это ты с
parachute and across the snow you glide so
парашютом и по снегу ты так скользи
nicely and in the summer along the Volga  we are also on the water
приятно а летом по Волге у нас по воде
with a parachute bang and
также с парашютом хлоп и
went look already 7 minutes 7 minutes And
пошёл смотри уже 7 минут 7 минут А
show there is snow here and already 7 minutes
покажи есть тут снег а уже 7 минут
have passed Show here The snow
прошло Покажи тут Снег
has melted So and on the head on the head
растаял Так а на голове на голове
there is snow left yes show yes and also the top of the
остался снег да покажи да ещё вершина
iceberg Don't take pictures of the top of the iceberg you are
айсберга Не снимай вершину айсберга ты
an experiment damn  killed us again Now we
эксперимент блин убил нам заново Теперь
need I can throw it on
нужно Я могу е накинуть Давай ещё раз
Come on again come on now wait now I'll leave the phone
давай так сейчас подожди сейчас лефон
here Now wait I'll leave the
оставлю вот здесь Сейчас подожди я
phone here it'll be
телефон вот здесь
good here Okay I'll
оставлю буд здесь хорошо Хорошо я
wait
подожду
Come on come on with both hands there pour it on
Давай давай двумя руками там насыпь на
yourself
себя
okay and remember with you okay okay okay  okay
хорошо и пом с тобой окей окей окей окей
Glory to Ukraine Glory to Ukraine
Слава Украине Слава Украине
Putin neighbors listen connect listen
Путин соседи слушаем соеди слушаем
broadcasts Ukrainian
вещает украинская
organization today in your dove denazification will be
организация сегодня в вашем дове будет
carried out
произведена денацификация
and
а
here with The man
а вот с Человек
is coming The yeti snow
идёт Снежный
You are
сноу Ты крутой
really cool I say we have
реально Я говорю у нас
snow
снега вот
look here I am in the snow now here I have
смотри вот я в снегу сейчас вот у меня
snow on me  I won't take those because there
снег на мне я те брать не буду пото что
's no point You're really cool, you're a really
не блин Ты крутой реально ты реально
cool Russian guy and we're all so
крутой русский мужик а мы все такие
Russian and you're a good person too
русские и ты тоже хороший человек
Why are there so few of those too?
Почему Таких вот тоже
You specially twisted it so that the snow would
мало Э ты специально закрутил чтобы снег
melt faster Yes N now the snow is Tae on
таял Да Н сечас снег Тае на
me here it is
мне вот он
snow and what time is it for you now
снег а сколько у тебя сейчас
And I'll tell you the time
времени А времени
now is
сейчас
am And
ночи А у
you have it We have half a night here in Kazakhstan
вас У нас пол ноч у нас же Казахстан
Almaty is a little to the east
Алмааты немножко восточнее
well if
ну бы у
we have VM
нас ВМ
live or with someone
жи или с кем-то
I live myself Listen you said that you
мто сам живу Слушай ты говорил что ты
pour cold water on yourself  are you really
обливается холодной водой ты реально это
doing this Well, you
делаешь Ну не
can't always show me how to
всегда можешь мне показать как вот
get cold water and pour it over Well, I don't
набрать холодной воды и облить Ну я не
believe that this is possible It's
верю что такое возможно это
like damn, I was in another place right now  place I
как блин был сечас в другом месте я
just showed you well in the bathtub you can
сечас те показал ну в ванне ты можешь
go into the bathtub fill a bucket with
зайти в ванну набрать ведёрко воды
cold water and howl at yourself
Холодной и на себя выть
not now in another place I just
не бы сейчас в другом месте я сейчас два
poured out two buckets of water so but at home in the bathtub
ведра се вылил воды так а дома в ванно
not
не
vysh va Van or else we'll take a bucket of water
выш ва Ван не то возьмём ведро воды
we'll go out  street
выйдем на улицу
vyle The thing is that Van is not that there is
выле Дело в том что Ван это не то там
cold water Yes I SBO
холодная вода Да я СБО
Posri Yes how can a Russian person
Посри Да как русский человек может
pour water on himself let's get a bucket of water
облиться водой вот наберём ведро воды
vyle on the snow can you pour yourself pour
выль на снегу сможешь облить себя облить
yourself I don't believe I don't believe these are some kind of
себя я не верю я не верю это какие-то
fairy tales fairy tales Well here  these here on the snow lies
сказки Ну вот эти вот нане снег лежит
like this snow I already understood if you smear yourself with snow
так снег я уже понял снегом обмазаться
it will melt for a long time but to take a bucket of
он долго танет а взять на себя ведро
water and pour it on yourself is impossible It is
воды вылить это невозможно Это
impossible snow is the same as you beat it
невозможно снег - это тоже самое как ты
out with cold water Yes but you see
холодной водой выбиваешь Да но он видишь
it melts little by little
он так понемножку тает
not snow - it is the same  water the thing is
не снег - это та же вода дело в том то
that you quickly doused yourself with water and you rolled around in the snow
что ты водой быстро облился а в снегу ты
it's the same water only in a different way Yes but
это та же вода только в другом Да но
just when  the bucket gives out it immediately
просто когда ведро выдает она сразу
quickly falls on you
быстро на тебя
not just when you are in the snow
падает не просто когда ты в снегу
snow falls on you And when you water
пое снег на те А когда ты водо
you don't feel it
ты её не ощущаешь
you just listen And can you show me how
ты просто слушай А можешь показать как у
you have like well here is your bath like that there is
вас типа ну вот ванну свою типа что там
really cold water in you  in the
действительно холодная вода есть у вас в
bathroom
ванне
damn Here I was caught If we
ва блин Вот был попался Если мы с тобой
met another time I would
встретились в другой бы раз я тебе
show you how to pour cold water on yourself
показал как холодной водой обливаются
let's try it now damn it's fate You
давай сейчас попробуем блин это судьба
just understand you're such a normal
Просто понимаешь ты такой нормальный
person I'm a normal person
человек я нормальный человек
Let's show you the bliss
Давай негу показать холодной водой
I pour cold water on you
вливаю пото
because I'm in the wrong place  So what's the
что не в том месте нахожусь Так а в чём
problem with going out and pouring water over yourself in the yard?
проблема в том выйти и во дворе
Let's do it for the third time. God loves the Trinity. Let's do it.
Троицу давай
You had something
у тебя что-то там
playing there. Someone called you.
играл тебе кто-то звонил
Called you. Oh, it's snowing.
звонил вот оять снег
My toes are
на у меня пальцы на ногах
frozen. Show me your finger.
замёрзли Покажи пальц
Oh, if only you had  there was snow then I would have understood
Эх если бы у вас был снег то бы понял
it's cool really
меня крутой реально
cool
крутой
It
Он
snow on snow
снег о снег
fell if you make a snowball it
упал если сделать снежку в оно
gets into
попадает
Yes show me how I saw in cartoons
Да покажи как я видел в мультфильмах
children throw throw like snow
дети кидают кидат как снег
throws it won't work  I have I need
кидает не получится у меня Мне надо ещё
one more person to
одного человека чтобы
show You just put the phone on a
показать Ты просто телефон Постав на
bench so I can see you there on the
скамейке чтобы я тебя видел там там на
street And throw a snowball
улице Да и кидай снежку
[music]
[музыка]
[applause] I
[аплодисменты]
have a finger deputy I'm already
Уменя пальц зам я уже
exhausted Let's do it for the sake of this for the sake of
замучился Давай ради это ради дружбы
Kazakh-Russian friendship Friendship Show me
казахско российской Дружбы Покажи как
how how  make snow and throw I saw
как лепить снег и кидать Я видел в
cartoons in my childhood where rabbits threw
детстве мультики что там кролики кидали
bunnies against a
зайчики против
bear
медведя
snacks Yes show how snow and
снеки Да показать как сне и
[music] a
[музыка]
person
человек
still Let's find someone on the street now
ещ Давай сейчас найдём на улице кого-то
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
let's go don't wait by
пошли не подожди
the way now it's time I'll watch Oh I already have
кстати сейчас врем посмотрю О у меня уже
on  work soon
на работу скоро
Come on make a snowball yeah Well it's a
Давай лепи снежку да Ну так это
small
маленькая
Snowball So show me Throw it into some
Снежка Так покажи Кинь в какое-то
window Throw it into this window Show me that it
окно в это окно кидай Покажи что оно
will stick to the
прилипнет к
window you're somehow
окну ты както
weak man
слабо человек
take a normal snowball Make a
возьми нормальную снежку Слепи
normal big Russian snowball
нормальную большую вот русскую снежку
like this
такую
Okay come on I'm going to bed come on
прямо Ладно давай я спать пошёл давай
so take it  Put the phone down Make a snowball and
так возьми Положи телефон Слепи снежку и
show me a big
покажи мне большую
[music]
[музыка]
snowball Okay, in short, look now I'm
снежку Ладно короче смотри сейчас я
leaving the phone yes yes come on well done
телефон оставляю да да давай молодец
[music]
[музыка]
I understand You're
я понимаю Те
funny well I'm just Funny cool Show me
смешно ну я просто Весёлый круто Покажи
really in some kind of car or out the
вот реально в какой-то в машину или в
window what where  -somehow how it flies I
окно что вот куда-нибудь как она летит Я
want to see
хочу увидеть
it Do you want it Here Yes come on come on
это А хочешь Вот сюда
cool in short I have to go to
круто кароче мне на
work This is work Russian people are not
работу Это работа русские люди не для
born for work but for
работы рождены а для
life we have only
жизни жизнь у нас
one life and you m What do you
одна а ты м Кем ты
work for
работаешь
brain You know such a thing
моз Знаешь такое
brain walks and that's it
моз ходит и всё
pogi And more
поги А
specifically more specifically he drives the
конкретнее конкретнее выносит мозг
boss crazy the boss yells yells
начальнику по начальник орёт орёт орёт
yells And you
орёт А ты
say yell
говоришь орёшь
Can you shut up a little bit at least for
Ты можешь заткнуться немножко хотя бы на
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
a minute What is your
минутку Как называтся твоя
profession called I don't
профессия не
understand What do
понял Кем ты
you do for a
работаешь ви
living I understand Listen, show me how it is
мозги понял Слушай а покажи как вот у
in Russia because  that we have
вас в России потому что у нас в
very small apartments in Kazakhstan
Казахстане очень маленькие квартиры
Show us what you have in Russia  the apartments
Покажи какие у вас в России квартиры
are cool you are a great power we have
крутые вы Великая держава у нас
small ones just
маленькие просто
one-room apartments Listen I will tell you
однокомнатные Слушай я те скажу у вас У
we have apartments the same as
нас квартиры такие же как у
yours 70
вас 70
square meters 7 square meters ka healthy
квадратов 7 квадратов ка здорова
about k this is a very small apartment I do not
об к это очень маленькая квартира Я не
believe that such apartments exist show me a
верю что есть такие квартиры покажи на
70 square meter apartment major
70 квадратов квартиру мажорная
No  well I'll tell you this right
Не ну я те скажу так вот
here in
прямо в
Russia and there are 300 square meters apartments in
России и 300 квадратов есть квартиры
Moscow in Moscow there are 500 square meters apartments
Москве в Москве 500 квадратов квартиры
on two floors let's say he lives on the
двухэтажный вот допустим он он живёт на
very
самом
last floor so take Show me your
последнем так возьми Покажи свою
apartment show me your
квартиру покажи свою
apartment no I won't show you
квартиру не я показывать не
Show me the entrance then Show me the whole
буду Покажи тогда подъезд Покажи весь
entrance How about  you look interesting to me
подъезд Как у вас выглядит мне
[music]
[музыка]
here's the entrance like this To the very
интересно вот подъезд вот так На самый
top to the very top
верх в самый верх
[music]
[музыка]
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
walk around the second floor
пройдись второй этаж
this is
это
[music]
[музыка]
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
third damn, you have a cool entrance So the
третий блин классный подъезд у вас Так
fourth
четвёртый
[music]
[музыка]
there
там
flowers no go to the very fifth go
цветы нет дойди до самого пятого дойди
Well To the very
Ну На самый
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
top and this is wait and this is a floor there
верх а это подожди а это этаж там ещё
are more apartments on the floor
квартиры есть на этаже
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
I thought this was just an apartment Well show me the
Я думал это квартира просто А ну покажи
floor
этаж
even this floor I think this is one apartment
ажи этот этаж Я думаю это одна квартира
And this is a floor
А это этаж
[music]
[музыка]
whole Cool Well go walk around the whole
целый Классно А ну пройдись по всему
floor I want to see  what does the whole floor
этажу я хочу посмотреть как весь этаж
look like I think it's one apartment
выглядит Я думаю это квартира одна
Wow This is a whole floor eh
Ничего себе Это целый этаж э
how many apartments are there on the floor Show me Well go through
сколько квартир на этажа Покажи Ну по
all the apartments
всем квартирам
So how many apartments are there this is the
пройдись Так сколько квартир тут это
ninth third how many all the apartments
девятая третья сколько все квартиры
show me
покажи
Well all the apartments Go through all each Show
Ну все квартиры Пройди все каждую Покажи
me I'm interested in the doors how people are
мне интересно двери как люди дет
cool  very
классные очень
doors In short, I won't show this
двери Короче я вот это показывать не
because Do you have an exit to the roof or to the
что А у вас выход на крышу есть или на
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
attic, no less I'm going to sleep now I
чердак не короче сечас спать
'll go to work
пойду на работу
So what do
ехать Так кем ты
you do? Well, where am I working there? It's better not to
работаешь Ну где я работа там Лучше не
Listen, do you have something in  in the house besides the
стоит Слушай а у вас вот в доме кроме
entrance there are
подъезда есть там подвальные
basements Well I won't say anything
помещения Ну я не буду ничего
because as they say this is my house
потому что как говорится это мой дом это
I don't want to say anything No well
я ничего не хочу говорить Не ну подвалы
you have basements besides the entrance
у вас есть кроме подъезда
in any house there is a basement A  show me
поз в любом доме есть подвал А покажи
what your basement looks like
как подвал у вас выглядят
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
I wonder that won't
интересно вот этого не
work Why do you
получится Почему
need a
нужен
person and a key to the basement No,
человек а ключ от подвала Да нет у
you need a person,
тебя человек
it's all
нужен это у вас там в Казахстане всё
easy and simple to
легко и просто
get in Kazakhstan, you need to achieve it now
получить это сча надо
Can you show me the view from the window
добиться А можешь показать вид из окна
of the
на
city
город
city view from the window of the city
город вид из окна на город
Show me
Покажи
oh city Samara you better on the internet
ой город Самара это ты лучше в интернете
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
look Go on the internet
посмотри Зайди в интернет
and Oh,
и Ува
city It seems to me that the snow has melted Well,
город Мне кажется у нас снег расстал А
show me is there snow on you the
ну покажи есть на тебе снег
snow has already melted let's
ещё снег уже расставил давай
[music]
[музыка]
update Not me ka  that's it Okay, let's go to bed
обновим Не я ка всё Ладно давай я спать
no no no no let's [ __ ]
пошёл не не нельзя давай блин нормально
talk normally Let's do it one last time
общаемся Давай ещё последний раз
with snow not that's it let's go to bed we need an even
снежком не всё давай я спать надо парное
number of times to be in pairs so that there are always
количество ра до пары быть чтоб всегда
pairs this is
спары быть это
with no no That's it I'm going no no man man
при не не Всё я пошёл нене мужик мужик
Let's see the fourth time we need to
Давай посмотрим четвёртый раз надо
rub  snow
натереть снегом
Damn so If you saw the microphone forgot to
Блин так Если вы видели микрофон забыл
turn on If you saw how I controlled
включить Если вы видели как я управлял
this Then I will control you like
этим Тогда я буду управлять вами лайк
subscribe comment and send this video to
подписка коммент и скиньте это видео
all
всем
your friends
знакомым
subscribe to y Telegram right now and while
подпишись на й Telegram прям зараз овин
it's very and very important YouTube is busy with us
пок дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня нас
through scarg or in ny ban and very many
через скарг ор в ньй бан и дуже багато
videos I don't show people sometimes I don't show
вдео не показую людям вчасно не показуе
information about streams That's why in order for
информация про стрими Тому для того щоб
us to Mali operational links are written
ми Мали оперативний звязок пишиться
right now and while there in  telegra okm
прямо зараз а пок там в телегра окм
video shchet tezh va and useful information and
видео ще теж ва и корисна информация и
we pone you tma
мы пон вами тма
sing operational zvyazok nezalezhno in that
пой оперативный звязок незалежно в того
chi will show you about this YouTube Slava
чи покаже вам про це YouTube Слава
ukraini subscribe
украини подпишись